Kari Swarthout

Software Engineer

Driven and quick-learning Software Engineer with 3 years experience developing applications for various projects and clients. Comfortable designing for, and working with cloud technologies. Able to learn and master new technologies in both team and self-directed settings.

Contact

Address

3F-3 No.1 Lane 62 Hsinchu City, Taiwan, 300

Phone

(541) 335-9392

E-mail

kari.swarthout@gmail.com

WWW

kswarthout.github.io/resume

Languages

Working Knowledge

- Java
- C#
- SQL/NoSQL DB
- JavaScript/Typescript
- HTML5/SCSS

Basic Knowledge

- Python
- PHP

Frameworks/Technologies

- Angular
- Android
- Azure
- Firebase
- Git / Github

Work History

2018-08 -Current

AP Computer Science Teacher

Hsinchu American School, Hsinchu City, Taiwan

- Created entire computer science curriculum for 2 levels of high school.
- Planned course content, presented lectures, administered tests and issued grades in accordance with AP methods and cooperating educational institution.
- Taught courses using Java and Python languages.

2017-04 -2020-02

Software Engineer

Olympic Systems, Seattle, WA

- Collaborated with team of 3 to implement multiplatform reporting utility that integrates with existing business applications.
- Rewrote time and expense entry system migrating
 Silverlight-based application to Angular framework.
- Designed and wrote SQL business reports for internal and external use.

Education

2016-09 -2018-05 **BAS Application Development**

North Seattle College - Seattle, WA

2009-08 -2012-12 **Bachelor of Arts: Communication**

Washington State University - Pullman, WA